NALAN DUMAN

MATHEMATICS ENGINEER

Personal Profile

I am currently actively developing a mobile application with React Native. In the future, I want to do both native application and web application development. I admire the work done in the entrepreneurship ecosystem and I want to continue my career in this direction. Since I want to support not only individual studies but also my teammates, I also develop myself in leadership.

Contact Information

Eposta: dumann16@itu.edu.tr Linkedin: @nalanduman Github: @nalanduman Adres: Gaziosmanpaşa/İstanbul/Turkey

Competencies

- React Native (Intermediate)
- Javascript (Intermediate)
- Mathematica (Beginner)
- Python (Beginner)

Club Activities

ITU Entrepreneurship Club

Board Member, Entrepreneurship Ecosystem Coordinator • 2018-2019 R&D Member • 2017-2019

- I took an active part in both the event and the organization of the events for 2 years.
- I organized startup office trips for club members.
- I brought together people looking for internships and startups looking for teammates.

ITU IEEE Computer Society

Member · 2017-2018

• I took part in the organization of the international hackathon.

ITU Cycling Club

Member · 2016-2017

• I participated in the organizations.

Personal Interests

- Playing the Piano (2 years private lessons)
- Taking Analog Photographs
- Cycling (1 year club activity)

Academic Background

Istanbul Technical University

Mathematical Engineering (2016-2021)

- GPA 281/4.00
- I took Matlab, C programming course.
- I used Mathematica for my graduation thesis.
- I took the applied data science course jointly with Garanti BBVA and did group projects in this field.

Work Experience

Mobile Application Developer

Yesil Science · July 2020-Continues

 I work in most of the mobile application development processes with React Native.

Mobile Application Developer

Zippy Pay · March 2021-July 2021

- With React Native, I supported the development of 2 mobile applications in the front-end part.
- I made Internal Dashboard with React.js.

Software Intern

VBT Information Technologies · Aug 2020-Sep 2020

- I developed small projects with Kotlin and Flutter.
- A group hackathon was organized and we developed a mobile application with Flutter.

Mathematics Private Lesson

 I have been giving private mathematics lessons to primary and high school students for years.

Sales Consultant

Armalife Clothing

• I worked as a part-time sales consultant at university for a while.

Sales Consultant

I C Waikiki

 I worked as a part-time sales consultant during the summer at university.

Certificate

İstanbul React Native Bootcamp

Kodluyoruz Academy · August 2020

- Mobile applications were developed with React Native.
- I prepared a graduation project and presented the project.

Android Programming

Ismek · January 2019

• Mobile applications were developed with Java.

Java Programming

Ismek · November 2018

• Basic Java was learned and projects were developed on it.

Introduction to Algorithm and Programming

Ismek · November 2018

• Learned the basics of the algorithm.